[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "__________ is mainly responsible for popularizing emotional intelligence.",
    "options": [
      "John Watson",
      "Daniel Goleman",
      "Sigmund Freud",
      "Albert Bandura"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "EQ is used to measure",
    "options": [
      "cognitive intelligence",
      "memory",
      "emotional intelligence",
      "attention"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Experts suggest that EQ is more important than IQ.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Being able to put words to feelings refers to",
    "options": [
      "emotional responsibility",
      "emotional cognition",
      "emotional attention",
      "emotional literacy"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The first step in emotional intelligence is",
    "options": [
      "perceiving emotions accurately",
      "reasoning with emotions",
      "managing emotions",
      "dismissing emotions"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "According to nine-layer model pyramid, __________ lies at the bottom of the pyramid.",
    "options": [
      "Emotional stimuli",
      "Self awareness",
      "Self management",
      "Transcendence"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The mixed model by __________ claims that EQ is a combination of competencies, skills, and \"facilitators\" that contribute to how people express themselves, respond to challenges in their environment, and connect with others.",
    "options": [
      "Watson",
      "Goleman",
      "Salovey and Mayer",
      "Bar-On"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The transfer of emotions from one person to another is called",
    "options": [
      "social effect",
      "emotional effect",
      "social contagion",
      "emotional contagion"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Hochschild has given the concept of __________ using the example of flight attendants.",
    "options": [
      "emotional indifference",
      "emotional difficulty",
      "emotional labor",
      "emotional literacy"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Review of literature shows that __________ is associated with increasing levels of burnout.",
    "options": [
      "emotional intelligence.",
      "deep acting",
      "surface acting",
      "emotional literacy"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  }
]